原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     捍卫者联草
校对     奶卫联盟
时间轴     西查
后期     8T
总监     奶卫联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
柬埔寨  金边
不
No!
快走
Go!
那怎么回事
The hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
-我们得找人救治他  -不  你们得跑
- We have to get him help. - No. You need to run.
我叫丹尼  我在追踪手和会的人
My name is Danny. I'm hunting members of the Hand.
我觉得你是我要找的人
I think you're the man we're looking for.
铁拳
Iron Fist.
回家吧
Go home.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am?
你要打的仗  不在这里
The war you're fighting... it's not here.
在纽约市
It's in New York City.
不  不
No... No!
捍卫者联盟
第一季 第一集
关门了
Closing time.
回家吧
Go home.
拜托  夜晚才刚刚开始
Come on, the night's just getting started.
夜晚
Night?
该死
Shit!
不
No!
等等  等等  先生
Excuse me! Excuse me, sir!
不  真对不起
No, um, I'm so sorry.
-这是我的车  -现在不是了
- This is my car. - Not anymore.
到早9点  它就属于城市了
At nine a.m., it became city property.
只能在卸货区停车
Loading zone only.
-拜托  我可以开走的  -钩上了就没机会了
- Please. I can move it. - Not once it's hitched.
但你可以去49街的扣车场赎回
But you can come to the impound on 49th to reclaim it
晚六点之前都行
any time before six p.m.
劳埃德  你干什么呢
Lloyd, what the hell are you doing?
怎么回事
What?
有问题吗
We got a problem?
我昨天接到电话
I got a call yesterday.
又有一个制作人想拍你的故事
A second producer who wants to tell your story.
绝不要
Hard pass.
纽约喜欢胜利者  不管你高不高兴
New York loves a winner, and like it or not,
你抵抗了一个很坏的人  还获得了胜利
you stood up to a really awful person and won.
你知道多少公关会为这样的关注收钱吗
You know how much publicists charge for that kind of attention?
要多少钱能让它停下
How much to make it stop?
我就是说  你该考虑一下
I'm just saying, you might wanna consider it.
能让你有钱付账单  直到你再找到工作
It could help keep your bills paid until you start working again.
-我的账单不成问题  -现在还不是
- My bills aren't a problem. - Not yet.
你至少开始接电话了吗
Have you at least started answering the phone?
只有你能把那样大的个人胜利变成失败
Only you could turn that big personal victory into a defeat.
-你知道你的问题是什么吗  -这样开始的句子
- You know what your problem is? - Sentences that start like that.
你不喜欢你变成的东西
You're not comfortable with what you've become.
杰西卡  你现在
Jessica, you are now
-是个货真价实的超级  -别说英开头的那个词
- a full-blown super- - Do not say the H-word.
-杰西  -我已经够头疼了
- Jess... - I-I've got enough of a headache as it is.
我就是说  你该考虑回趟家
I'm just saying, you might wanna consider going home,
睡会儿觉  然后再回归社会
getting some sleep, rejoining society.
我这不跟你说话呢嘛
I'm talking to you.
我很感激
And I appreciate that.
-这里面是有威士忌吗  -是啊  那杯是我的
- Is there whiskey in this? - Oh, yeah, that's mine.
看来你鼓捣文件没白忙活
Looks like all of your paper-pushing worked.
给这位明星解开  把他带走
Uncuff the superstar. Get him out of my sight.
我不好
My bad.
这是你的
These belong to you.
卢卡斯先生  凯奇先生
Mr. Lucas? Mr. Cage?
-你喜欢哪个来着  我忘了  -凯奇
- Which do you prefer? I forget. - Cage.
-我认识你吗  -富兰克林·尼尔森
- Do I know you? - Franklin Nelson.
我负责你的案子  我们经常通电话
I ran point on your case. We spoke on the phone... A lot.
是你经常说话
You spoke a lot.
只要好使就成
As long as it worked.
-多谢  -感谢你朋友波比·菲什吧
- I appreciate it. - Appreciate your friend Bobby Fish.
我们都完成了不少工作
We all did some impressive book-cracking.
而且  你在监狱困难时期
Plus, you made it through a prison stint
没有动过粗
without throwing a single punch.
我相信这不容易  考虑到你的...
I'm sure that was hard for a person with your...
-我知道  -名声
- I know. - ...reputation.
-克莱尔会来吗  -这里只有律师能进
- Is, uh... Claire coming? - It's lawyers only in here.
那失陪  我还得去赶大巴
Well, if you'll excuse me, I have a bus to catch.
当然  还有一件事
Of course. Uh, just one last thing.
霍加斯-赵-班诺维茨事务所随时为您服务
The law firm of Hogarth, Chao & Benowitz is at your disposal.
如果您需要重新开始
In case you need help starting over.
我不会重新开始  尼尔森先生
I'm not starting over, Mr. Nelson.
我要向前看
I'm moving forward.
大家喊我福吉
People call me Foggy.
你就默许了
And you let them?
您是公开声明  50街和10街交叉口的
You're on record as saying that the new subway station
地铁站会是  "对社区有利的"
at 50th and 10th would be, quote, "Good for the community."
会是...引述  "对社区有利的"
Would be quote-- quote, unquote, "Good for the community."
博科威兹先生  以您专业...
Mr. Berkowitz, in your professional-
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你干什么  看我爆了你的头
'Sup, man? I'll bust your goddamn head!
-是吗  来啊  -想干什么
- Oh, yeah? Let's go, then. - What's up?
-想来挑衅一下吗  -来啊  上啊
- You wanna try something? - Come at me. Let's go!
纽约警局  散开  够了
NYPD! Break it up! That's enough.
-你  人行道上的  -是  长官
- You, up on the sidewalk. - Yes, sir, officer.
博科威兹先生
Mr. Berkowitz...
以您专业的意见  这对亚伦·詹姆斯好吗
In your professional opinion, was it good for Aaron James?
我们同情他们一家
Our sympathies go out to the family.
但这件事  是个不幸
The whole thing... It's very unfortunate.
您可知道您新地铁站用的产品
Were you aware the products used in your new station
对儿童有害吗
were hazardous to children?
-反对  -我重说
- Objection! - I'll rephrase.
恩德萨本有什么优势
What was attractive about Endexoprene?
强韧  持久
It's strong. It's durable.
-价钱是别的一半  -我毕竟是做生意的
- And half the price? - Well, I do run a business.
为了省钱  就值得危害别人吗
Is it worth endangering people in the interest of saving money?
所有材料经过了测试
All materials are tested.
那些发现一被公布
The moment those findings were made public,
我们公司立刻换掉了其他所有站台的灰浆
our company replaced that mortar in all remaining stations.
"一被公布"
"Made public."
什么意思
What do you mean?
你是指9月29日公布的一份报告吗
Are you referring to a report released on September 29th?
法官大人  他在要求我的委托人
Your Honor, he's asking my client
做出不合理的详尽回答
to respond with unreasonable specificity.
博科威兹先生  如果我没记错
Mr. Berkowitz, if memory serves me right,
您办公室于6月3日就收到了一份
your office received an urgent delivery
来自安全委员会的急件
from the Safety Commission on June 3rd.
那是三个月前
Three months earlier.
我好奇  那是否跟恩德萨本有任何关系
I'm curious, did that have anything to do with Endexoprene?
我毫不知情
I don't know anything about that.
法官大人  默多克先生
Your Honor, unless Mr. Murdock
若能证明我的委托人
can prove my client
真的收到了这些假设存在的文件  那
actually received these hypothetical documents, then--
重点不是收没收到
It's not about whether he received them.
而是他是否有意无视了它
It's whether he willfully ignored them.
法官大人  我要求将这份送达记录
Your Honor, I ask that this record of delivery
收录证据
be admitted into evidence.
-我经常收到这玩意  -哪样最糟
- I mean, I get a lot of those. - What would you say is worse?
为节省成本而无视数据
Ignoring data in the interest of cutting costs?
还是没有向法庭提交
Or neglecting to supply the court with records
或许能证明你有意危及他人生命的证据
that might prove you purposely put people in danger?
-包括这位年轻人  -法官大人
- Including this young man - Your Honor--
包括这位年轻人
Including this young man,
亚伦·詹姆斯  他可能再也无法走路
Aaron James, who might never walk again.
法官大人  我们想请求休庭
Your Honor, we would like a recess.
不需要  我说完了
No need. I'm done.
我觉得他也完了
I think he is, too.
一千一百万
$11 million!
谢谢你  默多克先生
Thank you, Mr. Murdock.
-不客气  -谢谢
- Oh, my pleasure. - Thank you.
我很为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
天呐
God.
-你还好吧  -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
我能跟你说句话吗
Mind if I tell you something?
当然
Sure.
那钱对你父母会有很大帮助
That money is really gonna help your parents.
但对于你  从今往后
But for you, from here on out...
只会越来越难  亚伦
it's only gonna get harder, Aaron.
要知道你现在是在马拉松的第一英里
You realize you're only at mile one of the marathon...
你知道吧
right?
每个人都会告诉你该有怎样的感受
Everybody's gonna tell you how to feel.
医生会告诉你保持积极
Doctors are gonna tell you to stay positive.
你的家人会告诉你不要自怨自艾
Your family's gonna tell you not to feel sorry for yourself.
你的治疗师会告诉你别生气
Your therapist is gonna tell you not to be angry--
我已经生气了
I'm already angry.
气谁
At who?
每一个人
Everyone.
我只想要回我的生活
I just want my life back.
那是别人给不了的
They can't give you that.
或许你会再站起来
Maybe you'll walk again.
我希望能
I hope so.
但或许你不会
But maybe you won't.
但随着生活越来越难  如果你还能撑下来
But your ability to get through it... as this gets harder...
那比强颜欢笑
that is a hundred times more powerful
假装一切都好
than slapping a smile on your face
要强大千百倍
and pretending like everything's just fine.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
听着
Listen...
没有人能把你的生活还给你  亚伦
no one can give you your life back, Aaron.
你得...自己夺回来
You have... You gotta take it back.
走吧
Let's go.
恭喜  默多克先生
Congratulations, Mr. Murdock.
谢谢  佩吉小姐
Thank you, Ms. Page.
没事的  你该为自己自豪
It's okay. You can be proud of yourself.
稍稍骄傲一下吧  我不会说出去
A little. I won't tell anyone.
你来采访的吗
You, uh, here for a statement?
是的
Yeah.
你想不想  边吃边说
You maybe wanna go... do that over a bite or...
好啊
Sure, yeah.
等我五分钟吧
Can you give me five minutes?
-默多克先生  -默多克先生
- Mr. Murdock... - Mr. Murdock, sir...
嗯
Yes...
你抛弃了他们
You abandoned them.
因为你  手和会赢了
Because of you, the Hand has won.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他们养大了你
After they raised you...
成就了你的一切
after they gave you everything you are...
你却让他们死去了
you let them die.
不
No.
No!
-丹尼  醒醒  -不
- Danny. Wake up. - No!
不
No!
丹尼
Danny.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
就是...紊流
It's just the... It's just the turbulence.
我觉得我永远适应不了
I don't think I'll ever get used to it.
-丹尼  -我
- Danny... - I'm...
我去跟飞行员问问
I'm gonna go check with the pilot.
丹尼
Danny.
你要不要告诉我你在想什么
Are you gonna talk to me about whatever's on your mind?
那个
Look, it was...
没事的
It was nothing.
你又尖叫起来了
You were screaming. Again.
我没事
I'm fine.
我觉得我们对"没事"的理解不太一样
I think we have different understandings of the word "fine."
我们追踪手和会几个月了
We've been chasing the Hand for months.
我们终于找到了一个据说能帮我们的人的线索
We finally get a lead on a guy who can supposedly help us...
我们赶到时却只能看着他死去
and we get there just in time to watch him die.
那不怪你
It is not your fault.
我让那女人逃了
I let that woman escape.
你没让谁怎么样
You didn't let anyone do anything.
不管她是谁  我从没见过像她动作那么快的
Whoever she was, she moved faster than anyone I've ever seen.
是啊
Yeah.
她出手也快
She hit like it, too.
肯定是手和会  是吧
It had to be the Hand, right?
我不知道
I don't know.
手和会可隐瞒了我很多事
There are a lot of things that the Hand kept from me.
他们不是那种会很容易解决的问题
They're not the kind of problem that's gonna go away easily,
但我们可以解决的
but we can figure this out.
一起解决
Together.
他们想在纽约干什么
What do they want in New York?
你得脱衣服  首饰什么的都摘掉
You'll need to disrobe. Jewelry and all.
抱歉让你久等
Sorry to keep you waiting.
那么上一轮测试的结果
The results of the last round of tests
你已经知道了吧
were explained to you, yes?
恐怕结果是决定性的
They're rather conclusive, I'm afraid.
也就是说...
And by that, of course, what I mean to say is--
我要死了
I'm dying.
我的血红细胞数量锐减
My red blood cell count has dropped precipitously
我所有的主要器官也都几乎要崩溃
and almost every one of my major organs is close to collapse.
现在还是这样吗
Is that still the case?
你要如何治疗
What can you do to treat it?
老实说  这样的衰竭简直超乎想象
To be honest, this kind of free fall is off the charts.
这话没用
That's not helpful.
而且答非所问
Or even what I asked.
很不幸  就算是对您这样神通广大的人
Well, unfortunately, even for someone with your resources...
我们也帮不了什么
there's not much we can do.
我还剩多久
How much time do I have left?
可能几个月  可能几周
Could be months. Could be weeks.
我觉得这会让我们得到更确定的答案
I think this should give us more definitive answers.
请
Please.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
天呐  该死
Jesus. Shit.
琼斯小姐
Ms. Jones?
我叫米歇尔·雷蒙德
My name is Michelle Raymond.
这是我女儿  莱克西  我们需要你帮忙
This is my daughter, Lexi. We need your help.
我帮不了
I can't.
对不起  我们都不确定是不是来对了地方
I'm sorry. We weren't sure if we were in the right place.
今天不行  可能明天也不行
Not today. Probably not tomorrow, either.
-走吧  妈妈  -我读到了你的作为
- Come on, Mom. - I read about what you did.
她才不在乎
She doesn't give a shit.
-我丈夫失踪了  -她就是个行走的笑话
- My husband is missing. - She's a walking shit show anyway.
-什么  -莱克西  够了
- Excuse me? - Lexi, please.
我们情况不好  他已经失踪一整周了
We are not doing great. He has been gone a full week.
-你报警了吗  -没有
- Did you call the cops? - No.
-为什么不呢  他们免费  -钱不是问题
- Why not? They're free. - Money is not an issue.
这不对劲  我确定  约翰像表一样准时
Something is wrong and I know it. John's like clockwork.
他是个建筑师  他每天早上都8点去上班
He's an architect. He goes to work every morning at eight.
晚上6点30分回家
He comes back home every night at 6:30.
但最近  他...
But lately, he's-
他变了个人  神神秘秘的
He's been different? Secretive?
-或许还有点紧张  -这不像他
- Maybe even a little nervous? - And it's not like him.
那是因为他出轨了  好吗
Because he's cheating on you, okay?
没什么可耻的  这种事常有
Nothing to be ashamed about. It happens all the time.
-你不像我那么了解他  -没必要
- You don't know him like I do. - I don't need to.
你来找我  我给出了专业意见
But you came to me and I'm giving you my professional opinion.
你需要的是离婚律师
You need a divorce lawyer.
多谢您抽时间  琼斯小姐
Thank you for your time, Ms. Jones.
是啊  多谢了
Yeah, thanks so much.
不管他在做什么  希望你能找到他
Whatever he's doing... I hope you find him.
打错了
Wrong number.
杰西卡·琼斯
Jessica Jones,
帮自己个忙  别去找约翰·雷蒙德
do yourself a favor and don't look for John Raymond.
喂
Hello?
陌生人  你好啊
Stranger.
我们要去喝那杯咖啡吗
Should we get that coffee?
等你是一场豪赌
Waiting on you was a heck of a gamble.
毕竟  说不定你本事不行呢
For all I knew, you could've sucked at this.
是吗
Yeah?
希望我值得你等
Well, I hope I was worth it.
你挺有潜质
You got potential.
潜质啊
"Potential"? Yeah?
里面有些日子真的很不好过
There were some really rough days inside.
但你的信  帮我撑了过来
But your letters... they got me through it.
我都不记得上次手写信是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I handwrote a letter.
-还有那次的那首诗呢  -天呐
- There was that poem that one time. - Oh, God.
-不  挺好的  -谢谢
- No, it was a good one. - Thank you.
美国非裔诗人
虽然是妮基·乔瓦尼的
I mean, it was also Nikki Giovanni.
-嗯  -我们不能都像你那么俗嘛
- Yeah. - We all can't be your corny ass.
我宁可俗也不抄袭
I'd rather be corny than to plagiarize.
我还注意到你的信有一点
There was something else I noticed about your letters...
你没说的事
What you didn't say.
-卢克  -我懂的
- Luke - Look, I know the drill.
男人进去了  你觉得有事不能跟他说
Man goes inside, you think there are things you can't tell him.
但不管哈莱姆发生了什么  我都会查明白
But whatever's going on in Harlem... I'm gonna find out.
我们不能再享受会儿这个吗
Look, can't we just enjoy this part a little longer?
我需要知道
I need to know.
哈莱姆发生了一些变化
Harlem's gone through changes.
那是必然的
It was bound to happen.
玛莉娅在做什么
What's Mariah doing?
你走时她在做的那些破事
The same shit she was doing when you left.
现在  你唯一需要考虑的  就是你自己
Look, right now, the only thing you need to worry about is you.
如果你是想要我去找份工作
Look, if you're talking about getting a job,
我完全有做那个的意思
I have every intention of doing just that.
做什么
Doing what?
做哈莱姆的英雄  你还怎么能好好生活
How does being Harlem's hero allow you to live an actual life?
我会有办法的
I'll find a way.
现在
Right now, just...
我想帮助大家
I just wanna help people.
我也想
I wanna do that, too.
但是算我自私  我希望你照顾好自己
But call me selfish... I wanna see you take care of yourself.
谁啊
Hello?
-真帅  -谢谢
- Good look. - Thanks.
抱歉打扰
Sorry to interrupt.
但很高兴你安顿下来了
But I'm glad to see you're settling in.
米丝蒂  见到你很高兴
Misty. It's good to see you.
见到你也很高兴  卢克
Good to see you, too, Luke.
你怎么知道去哪找我
How did you know where to find me?
开玩笑吗  你是哈莱姆的英雄
Are you kidding? You're the hero of Harlem.
要一起去走走吗
Wanna come for a walk?
-其实  -不会太久  我保证
- Actually, I was, uh - It won't take long, I promise.
2号上菜
Number two in the window.
上周的报道很不错
Great story last week.
校董会丑闻的那个
The, uh... thing with the school board scandal.
谢谢  是啊  埃里森基本让我自主
Thank you. Yeah, Ellison's pretty much given me free reign.
感觉这是我注定该做的
It feels like what I'm meant to be doing or...
不知道你能不能明白
I don't know if that makes any sense.
当然
Yeah. Of course.
看来你也在做你一直想做的
It looks like you're doing what you always wanted to.
是啊  跟尼尔森-默多克的日子相去甚远了
Yeah, it's been a transition from the Nelson and Murdock days,
当时是合作
from the partnership but, uh...
无偿案让我很开心
No, the pro bono work does make me happy.
-那很好  真的...  -要点咖啡吗
- That's great. That's really - Coffee?
-是的  谢谢  -谢谢
- Yes, thank you. - Thanks.
糖在左边  奶在右边
Sugar's on the left. Cream's here on the right.
-奶在右边  谢谢  -不客气
- Cream on the right. Thank you. - Yes. You're welcome.
-抱歉  -嗯
- Sorry, it got... - Yeah.
你希望你没把秘密说出来吗
Do you wish you'd kept your secret to yourself?
不
No.
我需要你知道
I needed you to know.
我不知道我觉得会怎样
I don't know what I expected,
但我知道我不能再隐瞒你了
but I... I know I couldn't lie to you anymore.
谢谢  谢谢你这么说
Thanks. I appreciate that.
你怀念吗
Do you miss it?
紧身衣  面具
The suit? The mask?
不
No.
感觉像我人生结束的一章
It feels like a chapter of my life that's closed.
我不后悔  只是...
Now, I don't regret it. You know, I just...
-我后悔我逼走了一些人  -不
- I regret that it drove some people away. - No, it...
那没有逼走我
Look, it didn't drive me away. I just...
我是觉得我们
You know, I felt like we should
该先整理清楚自己
figure ourselves out first or something.
我在努力
I'm trying.
虽然这些
You know, as complicated
让我觉得很复杂
as I feel about all this stuff, I just...
我觉得你该知道
I feel like you should know.
纽约警局在胜利
The NYPD is prevailing.
我每天都做报道  犯罪率在下降
I report on it every day, and crime rate's down.
我真的觉得
I really think
夜魔侠让城市更加安全了
that Daredevil may have made the city a safer place.
或许吧
He might have.
但现在  城里没有他更好
But right now, the city's better off without him.
有马特·默多克在更好
Well, it's better off with Matt Murdock.
说到这个  默多克先生
Speaking of which, Mr. Murdock...
我想就今天
I would like to take your statement
神奇的亚伦·詹姆斯判决采访你
on today's miraculous Aaron James verdict.
来吧
Hit me.
-不  -怎么了
- No. - What?
我们不能又来那套
We are not doing that thing
你大摇大摆地走进来像是住在这里似的
where you come in here like you live here.
-是你给了我钥匙  -是你不经我允许
- You gave me a key. - You took the spare key
就换了锁时拿了一副备用钥匙
when you changed the locks without my permission.
门坏了  我是帮了你个忙
Door was broken, and I was doing you a favor.
-有什么事  马尔科姆  -就拿点汽水
- What do you want, Malcolm? - Just came for soda.
-我们干什么呢  -我们不做什么
- So what are we doing? - We are doing nothing.
你接了案子  我看得出
You took a case. I can tell.
-你又散发光彩了  -我没接案子
- You've got that glow about you. - I did not take a case...
-还没接呢  -那是谁
- yet. - Who is that?
-别从我后面看  -好吧
- Don't read over my shoulder. - Okay.
是个建筑师啊
It's an architect, huh?
-又是出轨的  -可能吧
- Another cheater? - Maybe.
他妻子跑来  急着找他
His wife showed up desperate to find him.
她说了一堆我听过的说辞
She said a bunch of stuff I've heard before.
"他可干净了  这不像他"
You know, "He's squeaky clean. This is unlike him."
但然后我接到通电话
But then I got a call.
有人用变声器叫我别接案子
Someone used a voice scrambler and told me not to take the case.
你肯定可喜欢那个了  是吧
Bet you loved that, didn't you?
麻省理工学院毕业
Graduated MIT.
在迪拜设计了两座摩天大楼  在曼哈顿设计了四座
Designed two skyscrapers in Dubai and four in Manhattan.
他的确干干净净  你觉得她说对了吗
He is squeaky clean. You think she's right?
或许吧  或许他好人当烦了
Maybe. Maybe he's tired of being the good guy.
或许他去饮酒作乐了  或许他在跟哪个实习生鬼混
Maybe he's on a bender. Maybe he's knee-deep in some intern.
-恶心  -相当的
- Gross. - Very.
那你的线索有什么
So, what are your leads?
我没在找线索  马尔科姆
I'm not looking for leads, Malcolm,
因为我还没接案子
because I haven't take the case.
得了  你追踪过电话吗
Yeah, right. Have you tried tracking the call yet?
不是那样的  电话可以改线路
It doesn't work that way. You can reroute phone numbers.
或许他没有
I mean, maybe he didn't, though.
或许就是个普通人  想迷惑你
Maybe he's just a regular guy trying to throw you off the scent.
-或许  -或许他是个外行
- Maybe - Maybe he's an amateur.
我刚接到一个屏蔽号码的来电
I just got a call from a blocked number.
不知你能不能告诉我是哪里打来的
I was wondering if you can tell me where it was coming from.
你能想想办法吗
Is there anything that you can do?
我觉得可能是我爷爷  他老年痴呆
You know, I think it's my grandfather and he's senile
他可能是想联络我
and he might be trying to get a hold of me.
其实  我这里有份失踪人口报告
Actually, I have a missing person's report.
号码就在我面前
I have the number right in front of me.
我可以读给你听
I can read it to you if you want.
真的  太感谢了
Really? Thank you so much.
这年头谁还用付费电话
Who the hell uses pay phones anymore?
-在哪  -11街和49街
- Where? - 11th and 49th.
我知道这地方
I know this place.
如果那人在那个街区干什么见不得人的事
If your guy's doing shady shit on that block,
他肯定在这儿
that's where he is.
我以前吸海洛因
I used to do heroin.
我知道的不多
I don't know much,
但我知道人都去哪消失
but I know where people go to get off the grid.
-那么你要接了吗  -把钥匙还给我
- Does this mean you're taking the case? - I want my key back.
滚出我的公寓
And get out of my apartment!
还在当差吗
Still in the force?
虽然你扳倒了响尾蛇
Just 'cause you took down Diamondback,
犯罪还是存在的
doesn't mean crime went away.
是我们扳倒了响尾蛇
We took down Diamondback.
现在  我要扳倒玛莉娅和沙兹
And now I'm ready to take down Mariah and Shades.
有那么简单就好了
I wish it was that easy.
我知道他们在干什么坏事
I know their hands are in something.
或许你需要一个法外援助
Maybe you need another assist from outside the law.
-一个刚出狱的人吗  -那都过去了
- From somebody fresh out of lockup? - That's behind me.
我已经洗清了过去  没什么可隐瞒了
Now that I've cleared up my past, I've got nothing to hide.
我的团队在查
Look, my team is on it.
但哈莱姆需要你的帮助
But Harlem could use your help...
只要你跟那位往树上绑黄丝带的小护士
once you're done spending nights with the nurse
缠绵够了
who tied the ribbon round the oak tree.
你说你的团队
Your team, eh?
你走后  我被调入一个全市范围的特遣队
When you left, I got put on a city-wide task force.
貌似是晋升了
Sounds like a promotion.
我只能说  我的片区不止哈莱姆了
All I can say is my beat isn't just Harlem anymore.
别误会  这里仍是我的家
Now, make no mistake, this is still home.
-好的坏的都是  -这里发生了什么
- The good and the bad. - What happened here?
官方说法  25岁男性
Officially, 25-year-old male
被发现死在一辆停着的车里
found deceased in a parked car.
非官方说法呢
And unofficially?
我觉得有人在利用哈莱姆的年轻人
I think somebody's been using Harlem's youth
来进行  只能说是  深夜差事
for what can only be described as late-night duty.
-送货员  -可能吧
- Couriers? - Maybe.
甚至可能跟玛莉娅有关
Might even be related to Mariah.
你觉得是别的
You think it's something else.
上月有七起  情况都一样
Seven in the last few months. Always the same story.
哈莱姆20几岁的孩子  让妈妈搬出了经济适用房
Harlem 20-something moves his mom out of the projects
搬进了新罗谢尔的豪宅
into a nice home in New Rochelle.
现金首付
Down payment in cash.
有什么联系
What's the connection between them?
查了名字  问了街邻
Run their names, you talk to people...
不用抢  不吸毒  就是份不入档的新工作
No guns, no drugs, just a new job, off the books.
干什么呢  没人知道
Doing what? Nobody knows.
准备听真正可悲的部分了吗
You ready for the real sad part?
记得坎迪斯吗  差一点就指证玛莉娅了
You remember Candace? This close to testifying against Mariah?
她的死还未侦破
Murder still unsolved?
她是他姐姐
That was his sister.
现在只剩一个了
Now there's only one.
你真该听到他们母亲那哭声
You should've heard the way their mother cried.
你能让我插手多深
How much can you let me in on this?
我可以查明幕后黑手
I'll find who's behind it.
你是可以
You could do that.
你也可以帮助指引这个年轻人走上另一条道路
Or you could help guide this young man in a different direction.
就像老爹以前那样
The way Pop used to.
听说清空了克里斯珀斯·阿塔克斯大楼的那小子吗
You hear about that cat that cleaned up Crispus Attucks?
就是他
That's him, man.
听说他被关在了佐治亚州什么地方
Heard he was locked up somewhere down in Georgia.
保佑我  神父  我有罪
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
我上次忏悔是三天前
It's been... uh, three days since my last confession.
我骗了一个人  一个我爱的人
I lied to someone. Someone I love.
她问我  是否怀念那种生活
She asked me if I, uh, miss the life.
我的另一种生活
The other life that I led.
我告诉她不
And I told her I didn't.
承认撒谎
Acknowledging a lie
往往是找到真相的最佳路径  孩子
is often the best path to finding the truth, son.
这样的谎言
A lie like this one...
往往表明了犹豫不决
is often a sign of indecision.
表明你的心智和灵魂尚未统一
A sign that your mind and your soul are not yet aligned.
我在努力无视我的灵魂
Well, I'm trying very hard to ignore my soul.
"主所看到的与人不同
"The Lord sees not as man sees.
人看到的是外表
Man looks on the outward appearance,
而主  看到的是心"
but the Lord... looks on the heart."
可以详说吗  神父
If you could elaborate, Father.
无视不能改变什么  马修
Ignoring doesn't change anything, Matthew.
上帝知道你的心
God knows your heart.
让他进来  让他帮忙
Let him in so he can help.
-哪怕那颗心已经受损  -尤其是这样的时候
- Even if that heart is damaged? - Especially if it's damaged.
马修  我想坦白地跟你说
Matthew, I want to talk frankly.
-请吧  -你的另一个生活
- Please. - This other life you led...
你的心还在那里
is your heart still with it...
还是在那些陪伴你度过那种生活的人那里
or is your heart with the one who walked through it by your side?
艾丽卡  是啊
Elektra. Yeah.
我是很想她
I do miss her.
但我知道  她从我这里激发出来的东西是错的
But I know that the things she brought out of me were wrong.
从你跟我讲的她来看
From what you've told me about her,
我觉得她会对你过得这么好感到高兴的
I think she'd be happy about how well you're doing.
或许吧
Maybe.
或许她会说  我抛弃了那份生活
Or maybe she'd tell me I'm abandoning that life.
也随之抛弃了她的回忆
And with it, her memory.
你没有抛弃艾丽卡  你不是那种人
You're not abandoning Elektra. You don't have it in you.
你所做的  叫向前看
What you're doing, we call that moving on.
炼狱是死者去的地方  马修  不是活人
Purgatory is a place for the dead, Matthew, not the living.
对人释怀没什么不对
There's nothing wrong with letting people go.
她会找到安宁
She'll find her peace.
我祈祷你也是
I pray you find yours as well.
你一向喜欢这里
You always liked this spot.
真是奇迹
It's a miracle...
这个公园居然还在
the fact that this park even exists.
城市居然没有拆掉它  建高楼大厦
The fact that this city hasn't torn it down to put up high-rises.
这些人肯定很难想象
Must be hard for these people to imagine
整个曼哈顿岛曾是森林
the whole island of Manhattan as a forest.
荷兰殖民者
You know, the Dutch colonists...
当他们从土著那里买下曼哈顿岛时
when they bought Manhattan from the natives,
据说整块地只花了  24美金
they're said to have acquired the whole thing for... $24.
要我说  太多了
Ask me, they overpaid.
市长办公室的联络人  他准备好了
The contact at the mayor's office... he's ready.
-什么时候能开始  -三个月
- How soon can we begin? - Three months.
然后进入最后阶段
Then we move to the final phase.
那不行  现在不行了
That won't work. Not anymore.
-我们得更快点  -我们都说好了
- We need to move faster. - We all agreed.
-这个计划可行  -原来可行
- This plan, it makes sense. - Made sense.
安排是很费事的
It took great efforts to arrange this.
如果我们加速进程  就会引人注意了
If we speed the process, it will not be quiet.
我知道
I'm aware.
我去通知其他人
I will inform the others.
很好  顺便代我问好
Good. Send my regards when you do.
帮我把鸟喂完
And, uh... finish feeding the birds, will you?
他们今天饿了
They're starving today.
你们知道科尔在哪吗
You guys know where I can find Cole?
关你什么事
What's it to you?
再上一层
One floor up.
谢谢
Thanks.
我叫你们别再闹了
Man, I told y'all to stop playing!
我是来表示悼念的
I'm here to pay my respects.
凯奇
Cage.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
-你认识肖恩吗  -不
- Did you know Sean? - No.
但我认识你姐姐坎迪斯
But I knew your sister Candace.
我猜我也是来悼念她的
I guess I'm here to pay my respects for her, too.
这家人运气真好  是吧
This family's got some luck, huh?
在这里  坏事往往会发生在好人身上
Around here, bad things have a tendency to happen to good people.
你觉得你哥哥的死
Do you think your brother's death
会跟她的死有关吗
could somehow be related to hers?
不  我觉得不...
No. I don't think...
不  肖恩的事  更多是起意外
No, what happened to Sean was, um... was more like an accident.
-你确定吗  -是的
- You sure about that? - Yeah.
听说他找到份新工作
I heard he got a new job.
那我可不知道
I ain't know nothing about that.
我们不是无所不谈的  那是他的事
I mean, we didn't talk about everything. That was his business.
当然了
Of course.
你呢
What about you?
什么
What?
你情况似乎还不错
Things seem to be going okay.
你也找到了新工作吗
Did you get a new gig?
不  我现在还在找工作
No. I'm just in between stuff right now.
我总在忙那个  懂吗
I'm always on that hustle, though. You feel me?
懂
I do.
听着  我能帮你
Listen... I can help you.
假设地说  如果你需要什么
Hypothetically speaking, if you ever need anything...
我觉得你该走了
I think you should go.
去问这里的任何人  我做了什么
Ask anybody on this block what I've done.
或是我愿意做什么
Or what I'm willing to do.
你可以信任我
You could trust me.
已经太迟了
It's too late for all of that.
什么意思  太迟了
What do you mean, "It's too late"?
-没事  -孩子  永远不太晚
- Nothing. - Son, it's never too late- -
我才不是你的孩子
Yo, man, I ain't your son!
我说了  我什么都不知道
I told you, I don't know a damn thing.
不管你在做什么  你会让自己受伤的
Whatever you're doing, you're gonna get yourself hurt.
想想你妈妈
Think about your mom.
想想她已经遭遇的一切
What she's already been through.
我觉得你该走了
I think you should go.
唯一能帮我的办法就是把我也变得刀枪不入
The only way to help me is to make me bulletproof, too.
英雄已经来迟了
It's too late for heroes.
英雄是你说的  不是我
Hero's your word. Not mine.
-我要我的钱  -我知道  会给你的
- I want my money. - I hear you. I'm gonna get it.
给你到今天晚上
You got till the end of the day,
否则我会回来  砸点东西
or I'm coming back here to bust some shit up!
约翰·雷蒙德  我是杰西卡·琼斯
John Raymond, it's Jessica Jones.
我在回你的电话
I'm, uh... returning your call.
你记得你企图吓我的那通电话吗
You remember the one where you tried to scare me?
楼下的人说你在这里的
The guy downstairs said you were here.
哥们  我不在乎你在做什么怪事
Dude, I don't care what weird shit you're into,
我们得谈谈
but we gotta talk.
好吧  你会付出代价的
All right, well, you're gonna pay for this.
...模拟一个缓慢的欧元区经济体
...and help stimulate a slow Eurozone economy...
炸药
老天爷
Holy shit.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们做了安排  如你所要求
We made arrangements, as you requested.
你确定吗
Are you certain about this?
还有时间考虑
There's still time to think it through.
你走吧
You can go.
-世界上最伟大的城市  -是啊
- Greatest city in the world. - Yeah.
纽约人都喜欢那么说
New Yorkers like saying that.
不过  经历了这一切
Still, after all this time, I...
我不知道我对它是什么感觉
I don't know how I feel about it.
这就是它的妙处  它可以成为你需要的任何样子
That's the beauty of it. It can be whatever you need it to be.
你需要它是什么
What do you need it to be?
家
Home.
...周三中央银行保持利率不变
...Central Bank on Wednesday kept interest rates unchanged,
顶住了加入其他大中央银行的压力
resisting pressure to join other major central banks...
谢谢
Thanks.
就是一座城市而已
It's just a city.
你会习惯看着它们倒下的
You'll get used to watching them fall.
我们得赶紧下去  走楼梯
We gotta get down right away. Take the stairs!
快下楼
Get down the stairs!
你拨打的号码...请查准号码再拨
...you have dialed. Please check the number and dial again.